is there a time limit for my georgia car
wreck claim
hello my name is ty wilson i'm a georgia
personal injury attorney practicing law
in the state of georgia
and our question for today is is there a
time limit
on a car wreck claim and the short
answer is yes there is a
time limit there the typical time limit
is two years from the date of accident
or the date of injury however
there are certain situations where the
statute of limitations or time limit
can be less and so that depends
on did the wreck involve a government
entity
the city or municipality is a lot
shorter
than the county and the state which is
also shorter
and so if you have those unique
situations where
it's involved and the city
and or county and or state are involved
you're going to want to reach out to a
georgia personal injury
attorney as quickly as possible as the
clock is ticking and if you missed that
statutory
excuse me a statue of limitations
deadline
you're done they will not open that back
up
and so it's very important that you
speak with someone quickly
you may not be recovered from your
injuries that will not matter
you need to get something filed and so
you need to speak with a georgia
personal injury attorney as quickly as
possible hope that information's been
helpful
and we'll see on the next video